So you've ordered.
所以你已经订购了。
You've gone through all that stuff you've eaten your food.
你已经经历了你吃过的所有东西。
It's delicious.
这很美味。
Right it's been a great meal.
没错，这是一顿美餐。
Now you need to pay.
现在您需要付款。
Why do they make you pay at the end.
为什么他们让你最后付钱。
They should make you pay at the beginning when you're excited to eat right.
当你兴奋地吃正确的食物时，他们应该让你一开始就付钱。
You've you've eaten it all.
你都吃完了。
Now you need to pay at the end OK.
现在你需要支付最后确定。
You see a waitress over there to get your waiter or waitresses attention.
你在那边看到一个女服务员来引起你的服务员或女服务员的注意。
Watch them moving around the restaurant.
看着他们在餐厅里走来走去。
And when you see them looking in your direction can do this.
当你看到他们朝你的方向看时，就可以做到这一点。
Just like that whether you want something or if you're ready to pay to ask for the check.
就像这样，无论您想要什么，或者您是否准备付款以索取支票。
Do this.
做这个。
And when they return that when they recognize you when they acknowledge you they look at you.
当他们承认你时，当他们承认你时，他们会看着你。
You go like this can mouth
你去这样可以张嘴
that they will bring over the check or the Bill to you.
他们会将支票或账单带给您。
They'll go because they're far away.
他们会去，因为他们很远。
Right.
正确的。
You don't want to shout like that across the restaurant.
你不想在餐厅里那样大喊大叫。
You want to do it in a quiet way because usually the restaurant will have a nice a nice quiet quiet
您想以安静的方式进行操作，因为通常餐厅会很安静
quiet quiet atmosphere.
安静安静的气氛。
Right.
正确的。
Very important right.
很重要的权利。
OK.
好的。
So check please.
所以请检查。
Is the most common I think and this hand gesture goes with it catching the eye of your waiter or waitress.
这是我认为最常见的手势，这种手势吸引了服务员或女服务员的注意。
We also say if they're right here could we get the check.
我们还说如果他们在这里，我们可以得到支票。
Could we get the check.
我们能拿到支票吗？
Could I get the check.
我可以拿支票吗？
We'll have the bill.
我们会有账单的。
I'll have the bill.
我要账单。
I'm ready for the bill.
我准备好结账了。
Ready for the check.
准备检查。
Excuse me.
打扰一下。
Yes I'm ready for the check.
是的，我已经准备好接受检查了。
I'm ready for the bill.
我准备好结账了。
I think we're ready for the bill.
我想我们已经为账单做好了准备。
Sometimes we can add that too.
有时我们也可以添加它。
There are lots of different ways to say it but these are these are the basic ones.
有很多不同的说法，但这些是基本的。
OK.
好的。
And then she says Sure I'll be right back with that.
然后她说当然我会马上回来的。
So she brings it now maybe maybe I've invited my friend out and I really want to treat my friend.
所以她现在把它带来了，也许我已经邀请我的朋友出去，我真的很想请我的朋友。
I really want to treat my friend because I haven't seen him or her in a while so I'd say I'll get it
我真的很想治疗我的朋友，因为我有一段时间没见过他或她了，所以我会说我会得到它
I'll get it or it's on me in American culture saying it's on me.
我会得到它，或者它在美国文化中说它在我身上。
If you don't say something like that it will be assumed that you will pay for yours and I will pay for
如果你不说这样的话，就会假设你会为你的付出我会付出
mine.
矿。
Probably we will split the bill so usually we'll say Shall we split it shall we split it right.
可能我们会拆分账单，所以通常我们会说我们应该拆分它吗？我们应该正确拆分它。
Don't assume that I will pay for you and I'm not going to assume that you're going to pay for me.
不要假设我会为你付钱，我也不会假设你会为我付钱。
In fact in American culture it's very common for people to split the bill but we usually still will
事实上，在美国文化中，人们分摊账单是很常见的，但我们通常还是会
say this shall we split it shall we split it if I want to treat you.
说这个我们要不要分开，如果我要治疗你，我们要不要分开。
I can say I'll get it.
我可以说我会得到它。
It's on me or sometimes just MY TREAT MY TREAT MY TREAT.
它在我身上，或者有时只是我的款待我的款待我的款待。
Are you sure.
你确定吗。
That's very nice of you I'm sure.
你真好，我敢肯定。
I'm sure it's my treat.
我确定这是我的款待。
That's my treat.
那是我的款待。
Thank you so much.
太感谢了。
I'll get the next one.
我会得到下一个。
I'll get the next one so you don't have to treat people.
我会得到下一个，这样你就不必对待人了。
You can definitely split it.
你绝对可以拆分它。
You might have heard the phrase going Dutch.
您可能听说过荷兰语这句话。
Actually it's not that common.
其实这并不常见。
Now this is an American thing but I said we would come back to tipping.
现在你s 是美国人的事，但我说我们会回来给小费。
We have to talk about that for waiters and waitresses and often hosts and hostesses and also bartenders
我们必须为服务员和女服务员谈论这一点，通常是主持人和女招待以及调酒师
people who work in the bar.
在酒吧工作的人。
Their salary might be very low and they depend on tips.
他们的薪水可能很低，而且他们依赖于小费。
It's a very important part of a lot of services especially in America.
这是许多服务中非常重要的一部分，尤其是在美国。
It's very important for whatever reason.
无论出于何种原因，这都非常重要。
OK so if you go to a nice restaurant you've got a tip.
好的，所以如果你去一家不错的餐厅，你就会得到小费。
How do you leave the tip.
你怎么留下小费。
You can leave the tip usually in the check.
您通常可以将小费留在支票上。
They'll give you a receipt after they swipe your card they'll swipe your card and then they'll bring
他们刷你的卡后会给你一张收据他们会刷你的卡然后他们会带来
you the receipt.
你收据。
Right.
正确的。
With the amount on it and a line under it.
上面有金额，下面有一条线。
So this may be you will say thirty four dollars.
所以这可能是你会说三十四美元。
Right.
正确的。
And then you would maybe tip let's say you want a tip.
然后你可能会给小费让我们说你想要小费。
I don't know.
我不知道。
Seven dollars going to tip seven dollars.
七块钱要给七块钱。
OK.
好的。
So now you're going to pay 41.
所以现在你要付 41。
So there's a blank space and the blank space you write seven and then you add it up and write the total
所以有一个空格，空格你写七然后你把它加起来写总
and then you sign your name at the bottom and you leave that in the restaurant it's called the merchant
然后你在底部签上你的名字然后你把它留在餐馆里它叫做商人
copy the signed one with the tip and the final amount.
复制带有小费和最终金额的签名文件。
It's called the merchant copy.
它被称为商人副本。
You leave that at the restaurant and you take the customer copy the customer copy.
您将其留在餐厅，然后将客户副本拿给客户副本。
OK.
好的。
So there are two copies of the receipt after they swipe your card leave the merchant copy.
所以他们刷你的卡后有两份收据副本离开商家副本。
Take the customer copy.
拿客户副本。
You don't have to fill in the customer copy because it's yours but you can if you want to.
您不必填写客户副本，因为它是您的，但您可以根据需要填写。
So how much is polite to tip.
所以给小费多少是礼貌的。
Well I have here between 10 and 20 10 is considered pretty low for most restaurants.
好吧，我在 10 到 20 之间有 10 对大多数餐馆来说被认为是相当低的。
It's usually 15 to 20 20 is kind of the standard.
通常是 15 到 20 20 是一种标准。
If you tip 15 it's okay.
如果你给15小费，那没关系。
It's kind of considered getting a little low but it's OK.
这有点被认为有点低，但没关系。
So if they did an okay job as your waiter or a waitress then 15 10 percent if they really didn't do
因此，如果他们作为您的服务员或女服务员做得不错，那么如果他们真的没有做到，那么 15% 10%
very well maybe they weren't very polite.
很好，也许他们不是很有礼貌。
OK.
好的。
So you can tip 10 percent maybe but that's not as common.
所以你也许可以给 10% 的小费，但这并不常见。
Only if they did a terrible job and maybe they called you bad bad names or something.
除非他们做得很糟糕，也许他们会骂你坏名声或其他什么。
Can you tip nothing.
你能不给小费吗。
I've only not tipped maybe two times in my entire life because I had a terrible terrible experience.
我一生中只给过两次小费，因为我经历了一次可怕的可怕经历。
And you want to talk to the manager after that happens.
在那之后你想和经理谈谈。
Listen I need to talk to you.
听着，我需要和你谈谈。
The waiter.
服务员。
She didn't come to our table for 30 minutes.
她有 30 分钟没有来到我们的餐桌旁。
Our food came and it was cold and she didn't mention it.
我们的食物来了，很冷，她没有提到。
All right.
好的。
So we had a you know it's a terrible experience.
所以我们有一个你知道这是一个可怕的经历。
Then maybe you could tip to zero but that's pretty rare.
然后也许你可以给零小费，但这是非常罕见的。